David Pham

UX Designer

Be behance.net/phamous2day

github.com/phamous2day

in linkedin.com/in/phamdavid

💟 twitter.com/phamous2day

e. phamdavid@outlook.com | w. thedavidpham.com

UX EXPERIENCE

Georgia Aquarium Dive Log

Worked on a team of 3 to redesigned the client's site for iPad specifications. Met with stakeholders to refine the project vision, performed heuristics analysis to identify pain points, iterated user-testing sessions with dive tenders, and designed mock-ups of final user interface. The prototype accommodates 2 dive scenarios customized with 2 sets of equipment.

Fox Theater Refresh

Designed a mobile site to increase ticket sales and social aspects of going to the theater. Usability testing and research had resolved a major pain point in the online ticket experience by reordering seating sections.

Binders Boutique

Created an e-commerce microsite for Binders Arts & Supply. Card-sorting reaffirmed user flow and site map navigation.

UX SKILLS

Heuristic Analysis, User Research, Persona Creations, Wireframing, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Information Architecture, UI Design

TECHNOLOGIES

UX

Sketch, Axure, InVision, POP, Toggle, Balsamiq, Photoshop, Illustrator

Development

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, Boostrap, AngularJS, ReactJS, PostgreSQL, Python, MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js, Socket.IO

Videography

OpenShot, Avid, Final Cut Pro, Premiere

WORK EXPERIENCE

Year Up Atlanta: IT Instructor Jan. 2015 – April 2016

- Facilitated learning of courses in: Computer Hardware, Operating Systems, Project Management, and Network Infrastructure.
- Iterate curriculums to meet the needs of students, corporate partners, and ACE accreditation.

MailChimp: Support Technician Sept. 2012 – July 2014

- Replicated user issues in test environments and provided documentation to developers.
- · Resolved more than 50 customer issues a day.
- Consistently surpassed average monthly ticket quota by 120%.

AmeriCorps VISTA: Tech. Coordinator Feb. 2011 – Feb. 2012

- Provided IT support and troubleshooting for hardware, software, web, and network issues.
- Created videos, online quizzes, guides, and live presentations to serve as engaging professional development workshops for teachers.
- Conceptualized and created school's first E-Yearbook to offset traditional yearbook costs (ink, shipping, page count, etc.).
- Taught 2 after-school courses: E-Year Book and Technology Club

EDUCATION

General Assembly

User Experience Design Immersive 2016-2017

DigitalCrafts

MEAN Stack Development 2016-2016

Georgia State University

Certificate CIS 2012-2014

University of Hawai'i at Mānoa

Bachelor of Arts, Journalism 2006-2010